

Contact

E alpesh18patel@hotmail.co.uk

P +44 (0)7845 653 712

Education & Training

UNIVERSITY 2009 - 13

University of Plymouth 2:1 (BA) Marketing

SCHOOL 1994 - 08

Berkhamsted School 3 A Levels - 11 GCSE's

Skills

Google Slides/PowerPoint TGI/GWI Photoshop/InDesign

Clients

Johnnie Walker, Diageo Innovation, Freeview, Tanqueray, Seedlip, Sky Broadband, Sky Mobile, RAF, Xero, Cabinet Office, Lynx, Dunelm, Amazon Prime Video, Uber, World of Tanks, Magnum, Harley-Davidson, Live Nation.

Interests

4-star rating at Ed Fringe Vinyl enthusiast Keen veg grower Novice fermenter

Alpesh Patel

Brand Strategist

Profile

I'm an accomplished and self-motivated strategist with nine years' experience within a mix of different agencies. Over the last seven years, I have honed my skills in brand strategy. I am looking for a new opportunity, with a diverse and forward-thinking strategy team, to help on a range of client problems.

Experience

ANOMALY

SENIOR STRATEGIST

2022 - PRESENT

I currently work as part of the brand strategy team at Anomaly. I have led the strategy for a broad variety of opportunities and client projects including elevating Johnnie Walker from a ubiquitous spirit to progressive luxury icon and developing the brand architecture and communications for the first Black Label variant launch. I've also been focused on imbuing Tanqueray's new brand platform with meaning, helping them to become the symbol of magnificence in culture. I've led the thinking on these projects and helped answer complex strategic problems, turning client objectives into an effective mix of different creative outputs across communications, innovation, and editorial.

ENGINE

SENIOR STRATEGIST

2020 - 2022

I was trusted to develop the strategy for a variety of new business opportunities and client projects. I worked on repositioning Sky Broadband from rational utility to heart-filled entertainment, injecting flair into Xero, and turning RAF recruitment into enthralling creative. I led the above projects, helping to convert client needs into effective marketing communications.

MULLENLOWE

STRATEGIST

2017 - 2020

My biggest projects included working on a new strategic direction for Dunelm, developing essential Cabinet Office Covid messaging, and helping Lynx own attraction again. I was integral to forming the strategic direction on these projects.

SOLD OUT
 CONTENT STRATEGIST

CONTENT STRATEGIST
THREADS STYLING

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER

2016

2015